Ehab Tawfik

Game Developer

Cairo, Egypt | (+20) 101-861-6456 | ehabelbwab75@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Game Developer with **4+ years of experience** creating engaging games for **Android and iOS**. Passionate about building **fun, visually polished, and performance-optimized gaming experiences** through collaboration and continuous learning.

Fluent in Arabic and English.

Skills

Unity | C# | 3D Modeling | 2D design | VFX | SFX | Optimization | Problem Solving

Professional Experience

Game Developer - Sneet Games | Nov 2023 - Present

• Continuing independent development under the Sneet Games name, focusing on designing and developing better games with enhanced player experiences.

Game Developer - Squid Gun Studio (Remote) | Oct 2021 - Nov 2023

 Worked remotely as part of a collaborative team to design new game ideas and mechanics. Contributed to gameplay design, code optimization, and overall visual polish to enhance game quality.

Game Developer - Game 4 Life (Remote) | Feb 2020 - Mar 2021

• Gained valuable remote experience collaborating with a team to develop optimized, high -quality games with creative gameplay solutions.

Game Developer - EtE Studio | Apr 2019 - May 2020

• Founded EtE Studio, developing small-scale games, exploring advanced game logic, and programming techniques.

Education

Bachelor of Computers and Information Tanta University, Egypt | Aug 2019 – Jul 2023